Sword of Vengeance is a history film directed by Jim Weedon.
Returning to his homeland after years of slavery, a Norman prince seeks revenge
on his father's  murderer – his ruthless uncle, Earl Durant.
Gaining the trust of a band of exiled farmers, he leads them into battle against
Durant, exploiting them in his inexorable quest for vengeance.
As one by one they are slaughtered in the brutal battle, will the prince
sacrifice everything an everyone to fulfil his quest for blood?
Shadow Walker, played by Stanley Weber.
Durant, played by Karel Roden.
Anna, played by Annabelle Wallis.
Treden, played by Ed Skrein.
Osgar, played by Dave Legeno.
Romain, played by Edward Akrout.
Sword of Vengeance (Serbian: Mač osvete) is a 2014 British-Serbian historical action film directed by Jim
Weedon, his first feature film, and starring Stanley Weber, Annabelle Wallis, and Ed Skrein.
Weedon's action sequences, and the overall look of the
film, were inspired by samurai films.
While the action sequences and Weber's performance were reasonably well received by critics, most felt the film's dialogue
and overall story were subpar, with the caveat that aficionados of the genre would appreciate it far more.
The film explores themes of sword, revenge, medieval, saxons.
The tone is dark.